sciencehealthnews.com 2018-12-12

# Science Health News | Privacy Policy

### Your Consent

By using the Science Health News website (the "Website"), you consent to the collection and use of certain information in the manner we describe and agree to be bound by the terms of use as set forth herein. 

### Information That We Collect

_Information Provided by You_ : We may collect your personal information ("Personal Information"), depending on your use of the Website and what information you provide to us. "Personal Information" is information that can be used to identify you individually, and includes items such as your name, home address, e-mail address and telephone number. 

_Site Usage Information_ : We and our third-party service providers, such as Google Analytics™, may also use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how this Website is accessed and used (known as "Usage Information"). "Usage Information" may include the type of browser and device you used to access our Website, your operating system and application version, the web pages accessed by you, the time you accessed these web pages, preceding web page views, and your use of any features or applications on this Website. Statistical data like this helps us understand what is interesting and relevant to our Website users, so we can best adapt our content for our users’ benefit. 

_Device Identifiers_ : We also automatically collects an IP address or other unique identifier information ("Identifying Information") from the computer, mobile device, technology or other device (collectively, a "Device") you use to access this Website. Identifying Information is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device when you access a website and/or its servers, and our technology identifies your Device by such Identifying Information. We may use Identifying Information to administer this Website, help diagnose server problems, analyze trends, track users’ web page movements and gather broad demographic information for collected use. 

### Other Technology and Cookies

Like many other Internet sites, our Website employs cookies, JavaScript tags and Web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation of our Website, recognize you and your access privileges, and track usage of our Website. 

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. We use persistent cookies and third-party cookies. Persistent and third party cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Website. Persistent cookies make it easier for you to navigate our Website, and they remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Third party cookies are only used for short-term tracking. 

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you want to remove cookies, you may do so by following the directions provided in your Internet browser's "Help" file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Website, but your ability to use some areas of our Website may be limited and may not function properly. For third-party cookies, you may opt-out of these by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/). 

### Third Party Links

The Website contains links to other sites. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. By including links to other websites, we neither endorse such sites nor guarantee that the information they contain is accurate. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site to read the privacy statements of every linked website as the privacy policies of each may differ from ours. This privacy statement applies solely to this Science Health News Website. 

### Third Party Information

We may receive information about you from third parties that include our products or promotional offers if you opt-in to receive information from us. 

You may also choose to participate in a third party app or social media site through which you allow us to collect information about you, including Personal Information. 

### Use and Sharing of Information

We use the information that we collect about you for a variety reasons, including the following: 

  * Responding to your questions or comments;
  * Providing you with access to certain areas and features of this Website; 
  * Adapting content, advertisements, and offers we provide to you directly or through third-party partners; 
  * Improving the Website and our customers’ experience; and
  * Sending notices or information. 

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share any of your Personal Information with third parties without your specific consent. We may share non-personal information, such as user statistics or demographics, as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

We may share your Personal Information with our parent entities, subsidiaries and affiliates for internal reasons, primarily for business and operational purposes. NOTICE: Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may transfer and disclose information, including your Personal Information, Usage Information, and Identifying Information, including IP address, to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, users of this Website, or the public. 

### Security and Your Information

We use reasonable safeguards to protect Personal Information against loss, unauthorized use, disclosure or destruction and when transferring information for processing. However, please note that no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be absolutely secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information to you transmit to us. 

### Our Children’s Policy

We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13. We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who address our Website. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. 

### Notification of Changes

The practices and policies contained in this Policy are subject to change at any time without prior notice. If we decide to change our policies, we will post those changes on this Website. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the Policy in place at the time such information is collected notwithstanding future changes to this Policy. The practices and policies in this Policy replace all previous notices or statements with respect to the same subject matter. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

### Applicable Law; Consent

This Website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the State of California and the United States, and is intended for the enjoyment of residents of the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. 

By using this Website, or providing us with any information, you (a) acknowledge that this Website is subject to the laws of the State of California and the United States, (b) consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable territories, in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive or equivalent to those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen, and (c) waive any claims that may arise under those laws. 

### How to Opt-Out of Target Advertising

If you receive targeted advertising from us, you always have the option to opt out of receiving future advertisements. You can opt out by visiting the "Manage Subscriptions" tab at the bottom of any emailed advertisement. Opt out requests will be processed within ten (10) business days. 

### For California Residents

Many browsers have a "Do Not Track" feature that allows you to instruct websites that you do not want them to track your online activities. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to this feature. 

California residents who have provided their personal information to us may request data regarding disclosures of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be submitted to us at the Contact Us tab of this Website. 

Please specify in your communication that you are making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.
